{
    "id": "af582ffb22284780a93c42682362922c",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………….. people agree with me.",
            "description": "Most and many are possible here with slightly different meanings.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Many",
                "Most of",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f552f2544d1048d694d4a1f47baca8d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We meet ……………………….. few days.",
            "description": "In a few expressions that refer to time intervals we can use every before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "each",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1b89f4c2a3a479d959eca8caf346272"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. these keys opens the door.",
            "description": "Before a noun with a determiner (my, this, any etc.) we use neither of.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d4cc7378cf94a78905ba9943fc5193b"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. people invited to the party didn’t turn up.",
            "description": "We use some, not some of, before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "026546c38c4b4af99fc5cca8cc8bc522"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. the shops remain closed on Sundays.",
            "description": "We use most of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a21157f48954c64a67fe4d72dc636d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. philosophy is concerned with life after death.",
            "description": "Much of is used before uncountable nouns that refer to a subject of study.",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ba636e05d554e89ba75c350060f7be0"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. his ideas are impractical.",
            "description": "Of can be left out after all, both and half when they are followed by nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a25b9e18c7b64d43b2015a6ab0861b98"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. my children love pets.",
            "description": "Of can be left out after all, both and half when they are followed by nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Both of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3721dc34f90c4199a767467246d0482d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spends ……………………………. his income on video games.",
            "description": "Of can be left out after all, both and half when they are followed by nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Half",
                "Half of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9122480438504e30b7de9cab8f1b39f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. us love music.",
            "description": "We cannot leave out of after all when it is followed by a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0b6f761c810452c97340feac17f344d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. them was there.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd548df26b054f8e87c6934fb4e05ac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… these blouses is loose for me.",
            "description": "\r\nWe use every one of before a noun with a determiner. \r\n",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "Every one of",
                "Every of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c0552320ff14d19a2cf8c62669c737e"
        }
    ]
}